foreign
[Music]
Navin bought ICICI Lombard's Health
booster policy of 15 lakh rupees keeping
5 lakh rupees as a deductible here's how
it helped him during these uncertainties
daycare treatment
namin got severely injured he paid for
the treatment of the ligament tear from
his own pocket to cover up the
deductible amount
[Music]
inpatient treatment emergency ambulance
he did not have to pay anything
his treatment and ambulance expenses
were covered by the health booster
policy
wellness program with the wellness
program of his policy Naveen gets
rewarded for his healthy Behavior
donor expenses pre and post
hospitalization
navin's policy covers medical expenses
for 60 days prior
and 90 days posts a hospitalization his
policy covers the organ donors expenses
as well
reset benefit his policy gets reset to
the sum in short the health booster
policy helped Naveen cope up with
difficult medical situations you too
could benefit the same way for more
information visit our website
ICICI lombard.com
foreign
[Music]